Hello.
Where will you be from?
I'm from Crimea.  Where are you from?
I am from the city of Khmelnitsky.  Where exactly are you from Crimea
?
Sipatoria.
There now.   Yes.   It’s
calm there, because there is a
military airfield there, I think it was in
Saki.
Well, then in Saki, in Ivpatoria.
Well, anyway, around Ivpatoriya, where there are
lakes, there were also these radars
there, there were all sorts of things.
Ha.  What's standing here?
Something is flying in.
Where?
Around Ivpatoria.
What difference does it make to you?   I want
to rejoice.
Rejoice?  It won't work.
Damn, I'll have to wait for the landing.
Listen, is this really a problem
with gasoline?   Are
we having a dialogue or, in short, an interview?
It's up to you.  If you
turn on, there will be a dialogue.  If you are
shy, there will be an interview.  Look
, it looks like an
interview.  And where are you from? Where are you from
?
The city of Khmelnitsky.  I'm telling you,
how are things going there?   There
was an alarm today.  Arrivals are very
rare, about once every six months.   Yes.
No.
No way.  And when you have someday
, come on, let's take turns.  I have a
question.  You have a question.  I have a question.  Let's do it this way
.
No, you just asked me a million questions
Milnne
was asked a million questions.  Let's
watch now, let's reset the questions.  I
ask, you I you.  And we will
calmly ask questions one by one.  Let
me just ask three more questions
and then we'll reset.
Let's.
That would be fair.  Well, you just,
in short,
Yes.
Here.  And when anxiety hits you
, how do you feel?
We feel anxious.  Second question.
Here.  In short, in your area, does it only fly into residential
buildings, or does it
also fly into other objects?
It hits not only residential buildings, but also commercial premises.
Third question.
And commercial is commercial.
Cool.
Here.  And what about your businessmen?
Unhappy or okay?  Like, no
one is happy that Russia is
shelling our territory?  There are three
questions.  Okay, let's reset.  Now let me ask a
question, you ask a question.  I have a question.  Question.  Yes,
listen.  Here in Ukraine they show
videos that in Crimea there is some kind of
problem with gasoline and almost
monstrous prices for gasoline.  How
true is this and what are the prices for gasoline now?   It's
not true at all.
What are the prices for gasoline then?
90 rubles  per liter.
Well, go ahead and ask your question.
Well, you do it yourself.
Well, 90 rubles.  There are no such prices per liter in Crimea
.
How do you know?  Because I have
relatives in Crimea.  In Saki, just like that.
In Saki,
yes.
It's a shame you have
relatives in that area. That's why I'm talking
about 90.
Listen, how are you doing with gas?
How much is gasoline?
Fine.  70 hryvnia.
70 hryvnia.  How much is this in dollars?
Calculate it in dollars.  I don't
use dollars.  I have hryvnias.  What about the
dollar-hryvnia exchange rate?
I don't know.  I have hryvnia in the country.
Well, what is the dollar exchange rate?
Well, I don't know.  If you want, find out.  I
asked you in rubles, you said rubles.
I didn't ask what the dollar exchange rate was.   Do
n't you know?  Yes.   Yes.
Well, it turns out cheaper than in Crimea,
because my relatives in Saki
thought that they were saying, yes, that it
turns out more expensive there.
And it would be cheaper to go to Ukraine.
Of course, they won’t go to Ukraine.   Why so
?
Well, because there are now, like, well,
border crossings and war.
And war, yes.  Well,
no way.
I don't know.  I thought we could go for a drive.
I was already thinking about going.  You
can go there once, yes, through Kherson.
Via Kherson.   It's
clear.
What, which one?  Let's move on to
my next question.  Yes, that's my question.
Why do you think Russia
can't protect Crimea from shelling?
Because there are not enough resources to
protect Crimea from shelling.
Understood.  Your question.
Why do you think Ukraine can't
defend itself from
ballistic missile attacks?  Yes,
because Ukraine does not have the kind of
resources that can shoot down ballistic
missiles.
Well, that's logical, yes.  In general, I’m surprised
how Ukraine is.
No, don’t be superstars, don’t.
No, no need, I do.  I'm surprised that
Ukraine has been holding on for all these 4
years.  I asked for an answer to the question.
This is an extended answer.  Come on, don't be
nervous.  Now my question.  My
question.  I didn't ask for answers.
My question.
They answered.  They answered.  I can also
give extended comments.   Okay
, I got it.  Yeah, okay, baby.  My
question.
You're a baby yourself, understand?
Why are you so nervous?
And what year of birth did you
start inviting?
What year were you born?  What did you
cross?
I asked you a question.  I ask a question.
What year did you ask the question?  You started to say
something and started to tell something.  I did
n't ask for this.   That's it
, forget it.  I ask my question.
What year were you born?
This is your question,
right?  Eighty-seventh.
I'm eighty-first.  So you're
my baby, huh?
Now your question.
[clears throat]
[sighs heavily]
Okay, dad.
Listen, dad,
since you're older than me, tell me, when will
your first army in the world defeat us?
Well, unfortunately, we are not the first army in the
world, yes, and we cannot name the exact,
say, date of victory, yes.  Well, it would be
funny if it could be
said like that, on May 9th of such and such a year we will
defeat Russia.  Nobody knows when
this will be.  That is, this process, well, is
impossible to predict.
Ah, there is no answer, it turns out.
Well, yes, there is no answer.  Now my question.
Come on, come on.  Why did Russia flee from
Kherson, from Kharkov, and
from Kyiv?
Tactical retreat.   A
clever move.  Ask your question.
Fine.
Still, tell me, please, when will you
defeat us?
I'm telling you, I don't know.  And I don't have an
answer to this question.  Well, really, no.
If there was an answer to the question, I would be
, in short, a complete failure.  Now my question.
What do you think?
I don't know.
OK.  OK.  OK.  Question.  Another
question.
Agree.  Let's.
Let's.  Look, you defeated us.
You are at
war.   That
's it, Russia is bombed.
Moscow is burning.  The Kremlin, Putin, as you
wish, died,
your actions.  What happens next?
Super good question.  So, look,
we don’t just need Putin to
disappear, we need Russia to disappear.
Our victory is not a change of power in
Russia and an end to the war.  Our victory
is the collapse of Russia, just like the collapse of the
Soviet Union.  That would be a victory,
yes.  Therefore, one should not confuse
Ukraine's victory with the cessation of hostilities and the
withdrawal of, for example, Russian troops from
Ukraine.  When Russia withdraws its troops beyond
the borders of 1991, it will
not yet be a victory; it will be the end of
hostilities, yes, but the confrontation between
Russia and Ukraine will move into different,
different dimensions.  As long as
the Russian Federation exists, yes, in its current form
, it will pose a
threat to Ukraine.
Okay, ask away.
I have a question for you.  What do you think will happen
to the people in Crimea if Russia leaves Crimea the same way it left Kherson
?
They will simply leave.
Understood?  Ask your question.
[cough][clears throat]
Tell me, so you won, as you
say,
and all these territories are there, what will happen
to the people there?
Good question.  Just like in these
territories, what happened after the collapse of the
Soviet Union?  They began to live in new
states and that’s it.  Lithuanians live in
Lithuania, Latvians in Latvia, Kazakhs in
Kazakhstan, Ukrainians in Ukraine.  Yes.   There
will also be an independent Tatarstan, and
Tatars will live there.  In Bashkartastan there are
Bashkorts, in Buryat there are Buryats.  There will be a
Ural Republic, a Siberian
Republic, a Far Eastern Republic, there will be new
countries.  And people will live the same way they
lived after the collapse of the Soviet Union, but
in new countries, not
imperialist ones.
Now I have a question.
Yeah, go ahead.  As a resident of Crimea,
don't you have the feeling that Russia,
Crimea, Donetsk, and Lugansk have somehow
abandoned these people?
Who has Russia given up on?
On the residents of Crimea, Donetsk, Lugansk.
Do you have this feeling?
I had this feeling
until 2022.
OK.   There is
no such feeling now.
Understood.  Ask your question.   There is
What?  What is he beeping?
Question.
Maybe it's Bimba beeping at you?
No, something is beeping from the refrigerator.
Defrosts.
Listen, well [clears throat]
look.
And if we imagine purely
hypothetically, well, like
in a parallel universe,
Russia wins against Ukraine,
uh, brings its troops all the way to,
I don’t know, Transcarpathia, there, back and forth.
Well, let's just imagine it in a parallel
universe.  I'm not saying it will happen
.  Well, just, what if,
uh, what will people like
you do, like other people who
supported Ukraine and the like, what will they
do?
Okay, just Yes.  Yes.  Look, it's very
logical, yes, if Russia wins, yes, and
ends up occupying Ukraine, it will be the
end of Ukrainian statehood, yes,
Ukraine in the form it was will
no longer exist.  It will
exist as part of Russia.  It
will be incorporated in Russia.  Uh, a huge
number of people
will simply leave Ukraine, yes, just like they left the occupied
territories, yes, there will be a mass exodus of the
population.  So, uh, let's say, Ukraine
as such will no longer exist.  Russia will not give up
this territory again, let's say, so that the
sprouts of Ukrainianism can grow there.  She already
understands that this cannot be allowed,
because sooner or later Ukraine will
fall out of orbit again.  That is why, yes, the
Ukraine project will then be completed by
Russia.  This is logical.
Answered your question.  Yes, yes,
yes.  I have a question for you.  Uh,
during the special military operation, yes,
since 22, Putin was
in Crimea?  Well, except somewhere on the
Crimean Bridge?
twice, yes, there was,
when,
well, I don’t remember exactly, but there on
[clears throat] that when that navy
was there, well, like the
fleet,
in short, there was twice
.  Well, at least twice.  At least twice
.
Understood.  Okay, let's ask the question.   Do
n't you remember?
I don't remember.  Okay, go ahead and ask your question.
Listen, if I’m still on the
same topic, well, purely hypothetically,
Ukraine loses [clears throat], for example, right?  Well, most likely,
she will win, of course.
Well, well, most likely he will lose.  Well, okay, that's a whole other
conversation.  Well, here's an example.
Maybe it's beeping your fridge?  You can
turn it off so that
Yes,
make it so that it doesn’t beep.   Well, in short,
he needs
work
.  [clears throat]
Still no sign.  [snorts] Let's
ask a question.
if he wins anyway.  Oh, wait, well,
let's come up with another one, in short, come up with another one.
For example, Ukraine won, right?
That's it, she got it all out there.  I think I
even asked that question.  Well, what
will you do next?
I told you, you asked this question.  Let's move on to the
next one.
I already answered this.
OK.
Just
curious, damn.
Let's communicate normally.  Question to
question.  Yes, let's ask a
question, a question.  Let's.
Well, look, you won.  Well
[clears throat]
no, wait, you're okay.
Ukraine lost,
Russia won.  Uh, they installed a
different president for you.  I just asked you a
question, what exactly will you
do, what will the bloggers do
there, what is it,
naturally, that I will fall under if
I cannot leave, yes, then I will fall under the
repressions of Russia, yes, they will most likely
kill me.  Absolutely right.  Well, that
is, if Russia takes over Ukraine, yes,
then I and people like me, yes, will
be physically destroyed.
Obviously.
Why
m
Why did you decide so?  Well, that’s what I
think, yes, because we are, let’s say
, a nuisance, yes, for Russia.
Existential war, yes,
yes, existential.  Now let's move on to the
next question.
What do you think, uh, if in
22 Ukraine
held Russian troops near Kiev,
held them back, and now
Ukraine is hitting
Omsk, the Moscow region,
Volgograd with its missiles and drones, today they tore apart a heating power station in the
Moscow region, yes, there are power outages there
.  Do you think Russia will be able to
win with such momentum?
Well, I think it can win because
Russia is a big country, and
I understand that Ukraine is cool, well, like with
drones and things like that
in various regions there.
Here.  You, well, for some reason they hit the WB,
well, like,
when they could hit, excuse me,
where to
go, for example.
I'll explain if you want.
Ab.
Well, okay.
PB is a commercial company,
not even a state-owned one, but Ozon is a
state-owned company.  And not a
single arrival on Ozone, bro.  so you know,
right?
Here.  Well, that's the answer, I suppose.
Yes, come on, and if you want, I can
comment on why they are hitting the WB, and
not the potets.
Yes, yes, of course.   Yes.
Uh, now it's Ukraine's task, as I
understand it, if Ukraine had 100
times more drones and missiles, of course, they would
fly along the T now, and in the zones, and so
on, yes.  Ukraine has adopted a very good
tactic, as I see it, not to spray,
for example, on different, yes, objects, but
to destroy an entire sector, yes, for example,
not just two Ozones, two Wildberries,
yes, because from this Ozone will survive, and
Wildberries will survive, yes.  And when they
systematically knock out Wiberies, yes, that's exactly what they're doing
, yes, that is, a
huge number of sellers will go bankrupt
, yes, this will entail
many different problems, Wiberies will go bankrupt
completely, yes, and it's
already clear that, well, let's say,
Wiberies' fate is predetermined, right?  Eh, if they hit a
little Wildberries, a little ozone, a little
something else, it wouldn’t be significant.
Viber would stay afloat, yes.
Here.   they will
completely drain him of his blood so that
he collapses, the bank associated with him collapses,
and so on.  Now
the entrepreneurs have collapsed, after that the
ozons will take over and so on, right?  After this, the
tets will take over.  I think the issue with the
testicles has been postponed until the autumn-winter period.
And you will be our ones, yes, closer to winter,
when it is cold, when it is more
effective.  Because,
for example, sitting now in thirty-degree weather,
yes, there, for example, on a day without light, that’s
possible.
You're hot, everything's there, no, yes, well, like that's
possible.  And when it gets to -30, yes, that's
significant, because when we
had this winter in Ukraine, yes, you knocked out the
heating plant, yes, for us it was significant,
because we had to, some areas
sat there for two hours a day, the
lights were on, yes, the pipes froze.  Here.  And as I
understand it, both Russia and Ukraine
are preparing for this round, that the attacks on
shopping centers and electrical systems will take place during the
colder period, when they will be more
effective.
Well
, come on, I have a
question for you.
Let's.
You do understand that
or you don't?  Go ahead and say
that if, as Putin said there, it’s not
Putin, it doesn’t matter.  But the point is not that
Putin said this.  Let's
not pick on the fact that
Putin said this.
But what if it threatens the
country,
Yeah.
precisely its existence,
then why such a world?
I understand that Ukraine can,
[snorts]
well, that is, with its own capabilities, with the
capabilities of the European Union, with its
capabilities, it makes no difference, well,
somehow attack Russia,
bomb, there, no matter, here and there, well, it
will simply reach the point that,
well, you will reach, okay, to that point,
you will reach there, start bombing the Kremlin
and so on.  But what will this lead to
?  That you will simply be hit by a nuclear bomb.
Understand?  It’s not even that
Putin said it there, but it’s just the
fact itself.  Well, because if you threaten
the existence of a country, the country of Russia,
you will get, uh, if someone threatens
the existence of Ukraine, everyone will get it,
actually.  Like, agree.
Well, by and large,
let's ask a question about nuclear weapons.  Question accepted.
So, look, uh, in 22nd
year, we in Ukraine still
took questions about
nuclear weapons with a hint of seriousness.  Yes, it was careful.  Now
everyone understands that there will be no nuclear war
, right?  That is,
the statement about nuclear weapons is so embarrassing to everyone that it’s even awkward,
you know?  Therefore, nuclear weapons remain a
scare tactic that no longer works.  That's
all.
Ah, well, you mean you don't think it will happen?   It
won't happen, right?  Because after
Ukraine invaded the Kursk region, yes, there
was no nuclear war, in short, everyone just went
nuclear.
Well, okay, fine, God forbid it doesn’t happen, I’m
not arguing.  God willing.
And even a conditional nuclear bomb,
for example, what do you want to demolish?  Dnieper,
Kyiv, there, Kharkov.  Well, what will this change?
Everything that is in front of
you will be bombed the same way as it was bombed,
right?  You will get your nuclear power plants with
drones and missiles and that's it.  No, well, it’s just that
you, damn it, don’t seem to understand what a
nuclear weapon is.
Well, yes, I’m not fooling you.  I understand that it won't
happen.
Well, what if it does happen?   It
won't happen.  Look, here I am, look,
my answer is that there will be no nuclear war.   The
nuclear weapon was just a horror story
that no longer works.
All.
And we communicated so well.
Like, subscribe, comment.  Subscribe to
our WhatsApp channel, here is the QR code.  There,
news similar to that
on the Telegram channel is posted for those who don't have
Telegram or who don't use it for
other reasons.  Subscribe to our
WhatsApp channel.  am